A B O U T M E

I am an enthusiastic and driven IT Professional with over 3 years of Extensive experience using multiple standard programming languages. Having worked on multiple projects has helped me to understand the various stages of a project, along with enhancing my technical skills. I am now looking for my next opportunity in the field of Web/Software Development.

CONTACT

- 👔 39, Carrick glen Avenue, Flat Bush, Auckland 2019.
- 02041248991
- shubham.singh267@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Level 5 in Information Technology.

North Tec polytechnic College, New market.

2016 - 2017

Level 6 in Software **Engineering.**

ATC Vision College, East Tamaki, Manukau.

2017 - 2018

SHUBHAM SINGH

AGILE SOFTWARE ENGINEER

SKILLS



- JavaScript, JQuery, XML, REST API.
- Database: SQL Server, MySQL, PHPMyAdmin.
- UI/UX and More: Figma, Adobe XD, GitHub, Unit Testing, Azure.

Experience

WEB DEVELOPER | ULTIMATE WEB DESIGNS (2019-Current)

Developed web applications using PHP framework Laravel with MYSQL, ¡Query, XML, Ajax,

Polished my Programming skills in C# and Asp.Net.

WEB DEVELOPER (INTERN) | CRUNCH & FLOURIS (2018 - 2019)

Involved in the designing phase of the company website.

Developed UX and wireframes using Figma.

Developed front-end of the website.

Technology used HTML, CSS and JAVASCRIPT.

OTHER EXPERIENCE (2018-2020)

Operating and reviewing all CCTV footage incidents within campus. First point of contact for any escalations around technical issues. Troubleshoot for computers and CCTV cameras.

Direct Reporting and response through calls and emails.

WORK INFORMATION

GitHub: shubh0786

Portfolio: www.shubhs.tech/ LinkedIn: in/shubhamsinghnz/

ACTIVITIES

Attending Tech events, Hackathons, Code Labs. Playing Cricket, Producing Music.

ACHIEVEMENTS

NZTA Hackathon winner. Voluntarily software participant.

REFRENCES

Reference Available on Request. Happy to relocate.

CERTIFICATES

MSRD: Agile Software developer. LinkedIn: C# Developer.

LinkedIn: Asp.net Developer.